{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","address":"3980 Second Ave Unit E","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC","licenseNumber":"229386","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":null,"establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000186F214B23C454C020BE99598A2C4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"41941","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","inspectionDate":"2018-04-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41941","inspectionDate":"4/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"10 foot candles","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"41941","inspectionDate":"4/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"41941","inspectionDate":"4/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"inspectionid":"41941","inspectionDate":"4/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."}]},{"inspectionid":"41031","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","inspectionDate":"2017-11-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inspectorid":"122","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"5","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"5","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41031","inspectionDate":"11/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"wall covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Smooth","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Wall(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"41031","inspectionDate":"11/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"WARE WASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."},{"inspectionid":"41031","inspectionDate":"11/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"41031","inspectionDate":"11/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"20 foot candles","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Lights","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"41031","inspectionDate":"11/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"inspectionid":"41031","inspectionDate":"11/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5372","name":"Foundation Rock Spirits LLC dba Castalia","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Sink","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"AIR GAP","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5372"}}